

# JEREMIAH MARTIN

# • DETAILS •

Lancaster, 17540
United States
7174068009
jeremiahmartin117@gmail.com

#### • LINKS •

GitHub

<u>Portfolio</u>

PDGA 128334

# SKILLS

Communication Skills

Detail oriented

Computer proficient

Self driven

Willingness to learn

Adept multi-tasker

**Team Orientated** 

**Promptness** 

Positive attitude

**Customer Service** 

# LANGUAGES

Javascript(node.js, jquery)

CSS

HTML

Git

# HOBBIES

Disc golf, leatherworking, painting, running, reading, and creating.

# PROFILE

Excited software engineering student looking to expand my knowledge and grow as a programmer by applying my knowledge in the real world. Experienced with front-end user-level programming. Completed aeronautical college during the Covid 19 pandemic. Former US Army Sargent with 6 years of leading soldiers and repairing helicopters.

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### UH-60M Blackhawk Helicopter Repairer at US Army, Fort Riley, KS

June 2013 — June 2019

- Managed the maintenance of 10 helicopters, ensuring they remain ready to fly.
- Logged over 700 hours as a flying crew member.
- Direct supervisor of 5 soldiers.
- Properly disassembled and reassembled complex parts.
- Remained punctual, reliable, and adaptable.
- Worked well independently and also with others.
- Performed scheduled maintenance, unscheduled maintenance, and made repairs or replacements as necessary.

# Smoothie Server at Central Market Juice Company, Lancaster, PA

August 2021 — Present

- Prepared specialty fruit smoothies in a fast-paced environment.
- Complied with all restaurant rules, policies, and regulations.
- Continually aimed to be reliable and punctual.

#### EDUCATION

# Airframe and Powertrain License, Spartan college of Aeronautics and Technology, Tulsa, Ok

March 2018 — July 2020

This was a hybrid program that is part online, allowing me to work full time, and in the 2019 fall semester begin on the ground with hands-on training. This license will empower me to have the skills and knowledge to fix and maintain all types of aircraft.

# Aviation Maintenance Associates , Spartan college of Aeronautics and Technology, Broken Arrow

April 2020 — July 2020

High School Diploma, Conestoga Valley High School, Lancaster, PA 2009-2013

Software Engineering, Thaddeus Stevens College of Technology, Lancaster August 2021- June 2023

#### **¶** REFERENCES

SGT Mike Bales from US Army

mike.bales17@tcu.edu · 2164699746



**Sue Ann from Central Market Juice Company** sueanny@comcast.net · 7179401049